Now I've taken weakness as my ally
I can fly to the highest heights
If I would just stop here
all I've lost would lose its luster
If you were lost out somewhere
at the same time my heart is shaken
Id have no way to find you
your kindness, or even your strength
I know
It's time for the dawn!
My peak performance
blow straight past in a blast, yeah
You'll be left frozen with laughs
The days of pain left in the past, let's hope
As Imake foes of the world
Em bracing myself upon shaking legs, yeah I'm
Just keep me going for a few more steps
Now, this is the comeback, the time to awaken is now
Battle on the rooftop of the Skull Dome, Onigashima,
in the skies above the Land of Wano.
The victor: Kaido.
Or, so he was...
Luffy!
Whoa, there...
All of you were incredible!
Truly unbelievable!
I am so overjoyed!
Been ages since I seen 'em, meow!
Them's those sky boat lanterns, ain't?
Oopsie...
Ain't no lie, yous-gara!
Luffy, by his own strength,
sent Kaido plummetin' into the bowels of the earth!
And, Momonosuke-sama turned inta a giant dragon
n' stopped Onigashima's descent!
Did I get all that right?
Indeed!
You're saying that pink dragon
was Momonosuke-sama?!
He's a Devil Fruit user?
It's been twenty years
since that day...
Since Oden-sama's tragic death,
since the start of our war t' avenge 'im...
An' now, we've finally won!
We took down two
Emperors of the Sea!
I didn't think I'd make it out alive!
Purrrrmeow mrrowmeow!
Meeeow!
Feels great, hunting the big game, huh?
Well, I ain't happy about it.
Captain...
Cap...
Captain!
Hey...
No clinging!
Straw Hat took down Kaido?!
He did it...
Luffy won!
Ya did it, Big Bro!
Yippee! Yahoo!
Luffy won!
Big Bro!
Everybody around me, going off
and pushing themselves to their limits...
Chopper!
Two seriously injured
people, incoming!
Chopper! Zoro isn't waking up!
Dr. Chopper! Please come here!
Aye...
Dr. Chopper!
We need you here, too!
The wound reopened!
Doctor!
Dr. Chopper!
Miyagi!
There's too many critical patients!
Okay! Let's take care of them!
We scoured the castle
for medicine and medical equipment!
Meanwhile, in the capital,
the lively festival is coming to a close...
Steady as she gooooes!
Say, Tengu-san!
What is it, O-Toko?
I heard my dad was
a super important guy!
And he knew he'd
get killed if he got caught!
But somebody said he went 'n
got himself caught on purpose!
I wonder why...
That is because...
Yasuie-dono gave
this country a fighting chance,
Had he not done...
...what he did that day,
all the lanterns of hope we had lit to that point
would have been extinguished...
Cover your children's eyes!
The last Daimyo to serve under Kozuki...
No, no... Ebisu Town's
happy-go-lucky guy...
...will be crossing over to the other side!
He sacrificed his life for the sake of
protecting the future of the Land of Wano.
So that you may live happily in the future
he and the others have guaranteed.
He did it for me...
Toko! Toko!
Toko!
Don't tell me...
...you ate the fruit!
I toldja not to eat that...
I-I'm sorry...
Toko...
Mind if Daddy has some?
Huh?!
You're quite a dancer!
You'll be the best dancer
in all of Wano someday!
Ya think so?!
Daddy...
For me? To live happily?
Tis what I believe.
Then I'mma...
...change my message!
This look good?
Aye...
'Tis much better...
Indeed....
There is...
...no higher honor for a samurai.
Steady as she gooooes!
Zunesha...
Zunesha, do you hear me?
I have given much thought to it...
I will not...
...open our borders, yet.
Understood.
I defer to your decision.
I have no reason to distrust you.
Mmm. Thank you.
Don't celebrate yet!
We still outnumber you!
You snooze, you lose!
Just give up!
There's no way Kaido-san could lose!
We're an Emperor of the Sea's crew!
Damn, they don't know when to give up...
You wanna go, huh?!
I still got plenty left in the tank!
Wait, Franky-san!
Shaddap!
Stop this at once,
Animal Kingdom Pirates!
You still do not understand?
Your lives were forfeit!
Young Master Yamato...
The one who stopped Onigashima from falling
after Kaido's Flame Clouds had vanished...
...was our very own...
...Commander-in-chief
Kozuki Momonosuke!
Whose side was he on?!
You have lost the battle
and your lives were spared...
But if you press your attack...
I will cleanse this world
of you thoroughly!
What is this tremor?
What is it? An earthquake?!
What's going on?
Babanuki-san!
What now?!
S-Something's wrong
on the sea surface!
Show me!
Yes, sir!
Why is this happening?!
The lot of you! Don't just stand there!
Go check on it!
Whaaaaaa?!
An undersea volcano erupted?!
The Battle in the Skies
over the Land of Wano...
Former Victor: Kaido.
The New Victor:
Straw Hat Luffy!
An eruption?!
That's coming from Udon!
What was that jolt?!
Are Kaido and his ilk
up to something?!
Something's flying this way!
No need to worry!
This is not a crisis!
K-Kaido... sama!
Why is he here?!
Today is supposed to be
our one free day!
My loyal subjects!
I am not Kaido!
Eh?!
The war is over!
That eruption was...
...the final beat of the drum, signaling...
...the end of Kaido, Supreme Commander
of the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
Where did the dragon go?!
H-Hey, look!
There's people...
How many are there?
Huuuh?!
Komurasaki-sama?!
That can't be! Is she a ghost?!
We just held her funeral!
Is this for real?!
Or am I just dreaming?!
She is real! Real beautiful!
Boss Kyoshiro!
What happened to your
special pompadour?
And now...
'Tis a long tale...
...but we present to you...
the new Shogun
of the Land of Wano!
How is it possible?
Run!
No... It's not...
Stop!
There is no need to flee...
That dragon...
I do not believe it was Kaido!
Does that mean... a second dragon?!
Boss Kyoshiro!
Komurasaki-sama?!
How can she be here?!
What is happening at
the front of the palace?!
Please explain, Boss Kyoshiro!
Naturally, the two of you
are quite famous.
But I wonder, does anybody still recall us?
K-K-Kin!
VK-Kin'emon-dono!
Foxfire Kin'emon?!
>How?! Was he not long dead?!
Did he not perish
in the flames of the Oden Castle?!
What is he doing here?!
Is this truly all a mere dream?!
Have we crossed into
the Land of the Dead?
But when did we dies!
No! Who cares if it's a dream?
Anybody else feel like
something monumental is about to occur?!
Yokozuna!
Kawamatsu-sama, the Kappa!
Inuarashi-dono!
Even Raizo of the Mist?!
Nekomamushi-dono, and...
Ooh!
Kikunojo-sama of the Fallen Snow!
Boss Kyoshiro, what is the meaning of this?!
"Napping Kyoshiro" was naught but an alias I assumed
to evade the prying eyes of the world.
In actuality, I am...
Denjiro of the Nine Red Scabbards!
The Nine Red Scabbards!
It really is them, in the flesh!
They still lived!
The Red Scabbards have returned!
Did they not all perish twenty years ago?!
Toki-sama spoke the truth!
This is unfathomable!
Somebody! Prepare a Light Scroll!
Make haste!
All of Wano must know this!
A transmission from the capital!
One and all, to Bakura Town!
News from the capital!
What could have happened?!
Is this about the earthquake just now?
I was afraid the whole village
would collapse!
Hey! We've got bigger worries
than some broadcast!
What? What? What happened?
What is it?!
Communications
from the Flower Capital!
Project the Light Scroll!
What?!
Kaido's son?!
Yes! Pleased to meet you!
You wanna fight?!
D-D-Don't struggle!
You waste your time!
Does that mean...
Our battle is still not won?!
Nay, most certainly not!
I am not your foe!
have followed your exploits
in the news for so long!
I admit, there were many of you
whom I doubted were even human...
But now that I see you
in the flesh...
Uh, what about your horns?!
Did you say Kaido's son?!
Nami-swannn! Your savior is coming!
At any rate, I will be joining you
on your vessel!
I am Kozuki Oden, also known as Yamato!
'Tis an honor to meet you!
What?!
"Joining you on your vessel"?!
Mm-hmm!
I'm all for it!
I'm especially for it!
What a funny boy.
But I'm afraid that decision falls on the captain.
We cannot accept you unless he says yes.
That is true.
I only hope that Luffy
will make it through.
I got shivers watching his fight...
Witnessing his glorious visage!
It was like, whack, bam, ka-boom!
Oh, it was breathtaking!
Hey, let's split!
Yeah, it ain't safe here!
They'll pay us back, an eye for an eye!
Hey, stop!
Who, exactly, gave you
permission to leave?!
We don't wanna be slaves,
Young Master Yamato!
Halt, lest I pummel you into the ground!
Flight?!
That is a disgraceful act for a soldier!
Shut yer traps and stay here, grunts!
Or face my wrath!
He doesn't seem like an enemy,
that's for sure.
Say, what happens with those guys now?
My technique'll wear off once
the moon comes back 'round.
You mean, in a month?
Yup.
After a month, some o' the animals
go back to how they was before,
but some of 'em stay friends with me.
I see.
I suppose it depends
on their personality?
I bet they choose whichever
feels better to 'em.
Neigh!
Master!
I'm so much happier with you!
Horselina-chan...
I hope ya stay with me too.
But I dun want a servant.
I want ya to stay with me
an' be my mommy!
Horselina-chan!
Oh, Master... Thank you so much.
I'm so happy...
Horselina-chan!
You're holding me a li'l too tight!
Tama and Horselina...
I'm happy for them...
Yeah.
L-Look!
Komurasaki, Kin-san, and all the rest
are on their knees!
Who is that?
Twenty years have passed...
Since the passing of my father,
Kozuki Oden!
Father?!
DDon't tell me...
Though these years have
surely worn on you,
you have done well to persevere!
The Fire Festival shall not end!
Starting tomorrow,
you may do whatever business you please!
What?! But Orochi will...
You can drink all you want, too!
What?!
No longer shall you be charged
for well water!
No longer shall the factories
release toxins that parch the soil!
The Land of Wano is no place for slavery!
Momo... kun?
You need not suffer any longer.
Four more died at the factory today...
Maybe that will be me tomorrow...
Who's gonna break it to O-Tama-chan?
O-Tama-chan, I hate to tell you, but...
...your father and mother are...
Daddy... Mommy...
Rest in peace.
I'm gonna be just fine!
That tickles!
Woven hats for sale!
Does anybody need a hat!!
They's sturdy and'll last ya for ages!
It's a real steal!
D'ya want a hat?
Sorry, I don't have money.
Hats for sale!
Anybody want a hat?
Komachiyo, I'm sorry.
Couldn't sell a single hat...
May I have a hat?
T-Tengu-sama?!
You're an orphan?
Don't give up hope.
Just a few years more...
The mighty samurai, the Kozuki,
shall return to our land,
and when that day comes,
they shall vanquish the ogres once and for all!
Kozuki?
Indeed.
I'll keep goin'!
I'm sure the Kozuki'll
kick those ogres' butts!
So I ain't gonna give up!
I'll be fine!
O-Tama?
Master?
Tama!
We'll make it so this is normal!
By the time we're outta this country,
it'll be a place where
-you can eat all ya want!
The wicked rule of Orochi...
...and the days spent cowering in fear of Kaido
have now come to an end!
I crossed the ocean and met
strong, faithful compatriots!
Alongside the Ninja-Pirate-Mink-Samurai Alliance,
I led a raid upon Onigashima!
Kaido, Orochi, and the
Animal Kingdom Pirates!
Every evil that plagues our fair land...
...has been vanquished!
Whaaaaat?!
Y-You-slew those monsters?!
That awful Orochi is gone?!
The what alliance...?!
I don't need to be afraid anymore?
Yeah...
Fresh water to drink!
I don't have to live through
that hell anymore...?
Finally... Finally...
And we will never forget all the brave souls
whose sacrifices paved the way for our raid!
Kin'emon, what do I do now?
I know not what else to say!
Just show off a little!
Are you just a puppet, Momo?!
There anything left in the world
for ya to be scared of?!
Th-
The name my father bestowed upon me...
...means "one without peer"!
Under my rule, even our parched, desolate land
shall surely turn to a paradise!
ask that you join me
in making that promise a reality!
Having crossed twenty years,
I have arrived to save you all!
As of this day...
I, Kozuki Momonosuke,
shall lead the Land of Wano!
Momonosuke-sama!
Oh, Momonosuke-sama!
Mother!
I shall remain true to my word!
Father!
I shall follow in your footsteps!
Momonosuke-sama!
The true shogunate has returned!
We've waited for so long!
Momonosuke-sama!
As a proud warrior sheathes his blade,
cherry blossom petals flutter...
...into the skies of that promised day.
This is the proud Land of Samurai.
Here under the night blossoms stands
a handsome man of eight!
Blessed with great
dedication and mercy,
albeit with strength that
leaves a little something to be desired.
This is the birth of the man who
would later be known around the world...
...as the Great Shogun of Wano,
Kozuki Momonosuke!
"Time's up'
Someone said again, with a laugh
Fine then, hide-and-seek playtime...
...is over
Let's go, come on (We can see it soon)
Let your heart beat out
and things will change (We can see it soon)
Grow strong, you have time
Lift up that dream
The overflowing loneliness can't sustain me alone
We were so free in our younger days
What a dumb dream
...to live
Shining a light on uncharte
Shining a light on uncharted ways
Get on our feet and try
Let's see the ends of the world together
Together, we can go and fly